let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question:
        "  In a quadrilateral, if one interior angle is 120° and the other three angles are congruent, what is the measure of each congruent angle?",
      answer: "B. 40°",
      options: ["A. 30°", "B. 40°", "C. 50°", "D. 60°"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " If the interior angles of a pentagon form an arithmetic sequence and the smallest angle is 120°, what is the measure of the largest angle?",
      answer: "D. 200°",
      options: [
        "A. 140°",
        "B. 160°",
        "C. 180°",
        "D. 200°",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 3,
      question:
        "Given a triangle with side lengths of 7 cm, 10 cm, and 13 cm, determine if the triangle is a right triangle.",
      answer: "A. Yes",
      options: [
        "A. Yes",
        "B. No",
        "C. Cannot be determined",
        "D. Not applicable",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "If a regular polygon has an interior angle of 150°, how many sides does the polygon have?",
      answer: "B. 10",
      options: ["A. 8", "B. 10", "C. 12", "D. 15"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: " In a triangle, if one angle measures 60° and the other two angles are complementary, what are the measures of the complementary angles?",
      answer: "B. 45° and 45°",
      options: [
        "A. 30° and 60°",
        "B. 45° and 45°",
        "C. 60° and 120°",
        "D. 90° and 90°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "If the exterior angle of a regular polygon is 30°, what is the measure of each interior angle?",
      answer: "D. 90°",
      options: [
        "A. 120°",
        "B. 135°",
        "C. 150°",
        "D. 165°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Given a quadrilateral with consecutive interior angles of 80°, 100°, 120°, and 140°, identify the type of the quadrilateral.",
      answer: "A. Parallelogram",
      options: [
        "A. Parallelogram",
        "B. Rhombus",
        "C. Trapezoid",
        "D. Quadrilateral",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "If the sum of interior angles in a polygon is 900° and it is a convex polygon, how many sides does the polygon have?",
      answer: "D. 8",
      options: [
        "A. 5",
        "B. 6",
        "C. 7",
        "D. 8",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "  In a regular octagon, what is the measure of each exterior angle?",
      answer: "B. 45°",
      options: [
        "A. 30°",
        "B. 45°",
        "C. 60°",
        "D. 90°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 10,
      question: " If a triangle has sides of lengths 3 cm, 4 cm, and 5 cm, what type of triangle is it?",
      answer: "D. Right",
      options: [
        "A. Equilateral",
        "B. Isosceles",
        "C. Scalene",
        "D. Right",
      ],
    },
  ];
  